chirpme.com 2013-06-30

# 

**  PRIVACY POLICY**

We at ChirpMe, Inc. (“we,” “us,” “our”) know that our users (“you,” “your”) care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously.  Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy.  **By visiting or using the Website or Services in any manner, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy, and you hereby consent that we will collect, use, and share your information in the following ways.** Any capitalized terms used herein without definition shall have the meaning given to them in ChirpMe’s [Terms of Conditions and Use](http://www.chirpme.com/privacy/tos?l=en_US).

This policy applies to ChirpMe, any subsidiary or affiliate, third parties (where applicable) and also applies to any platform, including but not limited to [www.chirpme.com](http://www.chirpme.com/), associated Facebook applications, associated mobile applications and any associated sites.  

This Privacy Policy shall be governed by the laws of the United States and the State of California.  Note that the English language version shall prevail in the event of any discrepancies with other language translations or versions of the Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions of Use for ChirpMe and any associated applications, whether on our website, any mobile devices, Facebook or other social networks.

**Use of any ChirpMe product in any capacity is acceptance of the practices described in this document.**

**I.           AGE OF MAJORITY REQUIRED FOR ALL USERS**

ChirpMe is designed for adults and you must be the older of 18 years of age or the age of majority of the country you live in to use our products.

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register for the Services (as that term is defined in our [Terms and Conditions of Use](http://www.chirpme.com/privacy/tos). If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for the Services or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to us or on the Services. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [support@chirpmeinc.zendesk.com](mailto:support@chirpmeinc.zendesk.com) or by contacting us at 185 Berry St, Suite 1050, San Francisco, California, United States of America. European users please contact us at ChirpMe, Inc. UK Limited, 72 High Street, Haslemere Surrey GU27 2LA, UK.

**II.         PROTECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION AND PASSWORD**

ChirpMe will not ask for your password- NEVER share your password.   If you lose control of the password you may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf.  If your password has been compromised, please contact us at [privacy@chirpmeinc.zendesk.com](mailto:privacy@chirpmeinc.zendesk.com).

Also, remember that you should exercise caution in disclosing personal information, whether in areas available to all users or in a one-to-one communication with another user.  ChirpMe is not responsible for nor able to control how other users or third parties may use this information.

**III.        INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE DIRECTLY**

We may collect information about you that includes but is not limited to the following:

a.              Contact information, including:

a.     Name

b.     Email

c.      Address

d.     Other contact information

b.              Pictures that you provide

c.               Friends and contacts, whether within ChirpMe or within another service application or social network

d.              Interests, including survey answers, social network interests, etc. from within our site and, where appropriate, third party sites

e.              Interactions with other users as appropriate, including messaging, gifts, contacts and other user-to-user data provided and exchanged within ChirpMe.

We may also collect financial information where appropriate, including but not limited to the following:

f.               Payment information

g.              Billing information, including address

h.              Permissions for re-billing

ChirpMe makes an effort to comply with all applicable laws and regulations regarding information of all sorts, and makes particular efforts to protect financial information as part of PCI compliance.

**IV.        INFORMATION COLLECTED AUTOMATICALLY**

ChirpMe uses a variety of technologies to collect information about your activities and use of our site from your computer, tablet, interactive television, game console, mobile device or equivalent.  This information may include but is not limited to your IP address, browser type and version, platform type, prior website visited, next website visited, mobile carrier, mobile device ID, phone number and one or more cookies that may provide a unique identifier for you or your device.

ChirpMe may also collect and collate information about your usage of and activity on our products and may share aggregated or anonymized information with select third parties to improve our understanding and your user experience.

**V.         COOKIES AND OTHER INTERNET TECHNOLOGIES**

ChirpMe may use various Internet technologies, including but not limited to web beacons and pixel tags to optimize your experience, prevent fraud, protect user experience and to track usage information.  These technologies may place small data files on your computer or mobile device. 

**VI.        INFORMATION COLLECTED BY THIRD PARTY ADVERTISERS**

ChirpMe may allow third parties to advertise on our site, and these third parties may serve ads or provide offers to users.  This may include the use of their own cookies, pixels and other Internet technologies.  These entities offer their own terms of use and privacy policies and are not governed by our Privacy Policy.  You may wish to visit [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) to opt out of participating services and to gain more information.

If you provide your third-party account credentials to us, you understand some content and/or information in those accounts (“Third Party Account Information”) such as personal information you have provided to the third parties or are contained in those accounts may be transmitted into your account with us if you authorize such transmissions, and that Third Party Account Information transmitted to our Services is covered by this Privacy Policy.

**VII.       THIRD PARTY SOCIAL NETWORKING SITE INFORMATION**

Use of ChirpMe may involve a third party social networking site such as Facebook, whether as part of a ChirpMe application or as a stand-alone site.  As such, the information you provide to ChirpMe is affected by any privacy settings applied in the social networking site.  Use of a ChirpMe product incorporating the social networking site data means that you authorize us to collect, store, retain and use any and all provided information indefinitely.  Use includes but is not limited to logging in through another social networking site, authorizing or accepting our application within another social network, or equivalent behavior.

**VIII.     HOW WE USE PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We use the information you provide and that we collect for the purposes previously described in this Privacy Policy and in our Terms and Conditions of Use and in all ways calculated to assist in the normal course of our business and your use of our products.

Specific examples of how we use such information include the following, without limitation:

·               To operate our products and services, including new products;

·               To operate your ChirpMe account, including pictures and profile;

·               To provide a safe and friendly environment;

·               To detect and prevent abusive behavior by other users or third parties;

·               To protect the rights, property and safety of ChirpMe and all users;

·               To provide customer service and assistance;

·               To communicate advertising and offers on our own behalf;

·               To allow third parties to communicate advertising and offers directly;

·               To provide a safe, secure and consistent payment experiences;

·               To perform other functions or provide other services as we deem fit;

Please note that we may propagate and duplicate personal information throughout the world for purposes of speed of delivery and to back up user data.

**IX.        SHARING INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES**

We do not share your information with third parties except as follows:

·               You consent to share- typically this covers the information you share on the site with other users (and by extension the general public);

·               We are required to do so by law or regulation, as we reasonably determine necessary.  This may include but is not limited to governmental request, our enforcement of this Privacy Policy, our Terms and Conditions of Use, our Community Guidelines, and other policies as we may see fit to create, or as part of a third party claim or allegation against ChirpMe.  We may also share information as part of our efforts to provide a safe, secure and functional site to you and other users;

·               We share with third party vendors performing work or services for us in order to complete their work;

·               You grant consent to share information with other third parties, as in making payment to us through a payment provider.

·               We may choose to buy or sell assets.  In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that would be transferred.  Also, if we (or our assets) are acquired, or if we go out of business, enter bankruptcy, merge with another entity or go through some other change of control, personal information would be one of the assets transferred to or acquired by a third party.

Note that we may share aggregated information with other parties where that information does not identify individual users such as you.

Under California Civil Code Sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice identifying the categories of Personal Information which we share with our affiliates and/or third parties for marketing purposes, and providing contact information for such affiliates and third parties.  If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to [support@chirpmeinc.zendesk.com](mailto:support@chirpmeinc.zendesk.com) or by contacting us at 185 Berry St, Suite 1050, San Francisco, California, United States of America **.** European users please contact us at ChirpMe, Inc. UK Limited, 72 High Street, Haslemere Surrey GU27 2LA, UK.

**X.          CHANGING OR REMOVING YOUR INFORMATION**

You may adjust, update or remove information on your profile within the various ChirpMe products.  You may also uninstall or remove the products and we will no longer share the information within ChirpMe with other users.

We will maintain a record of your account and information even after you terminate the service for a duration determined by us at our sole discretion.   We also reserve the right to retain information in relation to prior payment, allegations of misbehavior on your part by other users, allegations of fraud, or other issues that we reasonably determine may require us to retain your information.

Also, please note that some information may be available externally even after you terminate your account via Internet search engine or on other users’ accounts (e.g. messages exchanged, etc.), and that we explicitly disavow any responsibility in relation to such information.

**XI.        TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE IS HEREBY INCORPORATED**

This paragraph expressly incorporates and includes our [Terms and Conditions of Use](http://www.chirpme.com/privacy/tos?l=en_US) and other published policies as part of this Privacy Policy.  Please review the Terms and Conditions of Use prior to using ChirpMe.  

**XII.       SECURITY**

ChirpMe takes reasonable measures and makes reasonable efforts to protect your personal information and data to prevent loss, misuse or unauthorized access from other ChirpMe users and third parties.  However, you are responsible to inform us if you see anything that may be cause for concern.  Please contact us at [privacy@chirpmeinc.zendesk.com](mailto:privacy@chirpmeinc.zendesk.com) or at our mailing address with questions or concerns.

**XIII.      NO RIGHTS OF THIRD PARTIES**

This Privacy Policy shall not be construed to create any rights enforceable by third parties against ChirpMe or the user, nor shall it be construed to require disclosure of any personal information of the users.

**XIV.     TERMS OF USE**

This paragraph expressly incorporates and includes our [Terms and Conditions of Use](http://www.chirpme.com/privacy/tos?l=en_US) as part of this Agreement.  Please review the terms prior to using ChirpMe.

**XV.       COMPLAINTS OR SUPPORT**

Report any issues by contacting us at [privacy@chirpmeinc.zendesk.com](mailto:privacy@chirpmeinc.zendesk.com).

**XVI.      MAILING ADDRESS**

ChirpMe, Inc., is a company incorporated in Delaware under company number 4996742 and with offices at 185 Berry St, Suite 1050, San Francisco, California, United States of America. Please direct any American correspondence to the above address. ChirpMe Inc. UK is a company incorporated in the UK under company 08294818 and with offices at 72 High Street, Haslemere Surrey GU27 2LA, Please direct any European correspondence to the above address.

**XVI.      RIGHT TO MODIFY**

By continuing to use the Service after those changes become effective, you are agreeing to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy; if you do not agree to the change, simply don’t use the Service after the change is effective, in which case the change will not apply to you.

Changes to this Policy will be effective by posting revisions on ChirpMe products, including but not limited to websites, mobile applications, and applications within third party social networks and any other means as we may see fit to use.

Enjoy ChirpMe!

Last Modified

June 5, 2013
